{
    "id": "89e6ad59dd96444189c67b8e9be5b706",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I met him ……………………… Monday.",
            "description": "We use on before days.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "in",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "They took him ……………………… the doctor.",
            "description": "To indicates direction.",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "for",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Regular exercise is beneficial ……………………… health.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "to",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "There are many disadvantages ………………………….. living alone.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "of",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The cat jumped ………………………… the wall.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "across",
                "over",
                "through"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She swam ………………………….. the river.",
            "description": "Across indicates movement from one side to the other.",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "across",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You never listen ……………………….. me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "to",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Why are you staring ………………………. me like that?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "with",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He is rude …………………………. everyone.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "with",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "You can’t expect her to dance ………………………. your tune.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She recognized him ………………………. once.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "by",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He is enthusiastic …………………….. his profession.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "of",
                "about"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}